A Roaring Adventure with Blistering Action and Eye-Popping Women!
The Lost Empire is a adventure, action, fantasy film directed by Jim Wynorski.
A police officer and her two companions battle an evil genius
with diabolical plans to destroy the world.
Whoever can find the three sacred jewels can anticipate total power.
Angel Wolfe, played by Melanie Vincz.
Whitestar, played by Raven De La Croix.
Heather McClure, played by Angela Aames.
Rick Stanton, played by Paul Coufos.
Koro, played by Robert Tessier.
Dr. Sin Do / Lee Chuck, played by Angus Scrimm.
The Lost Empire is a 1984 American action adventure film written,
produced, and directed by Jim Wynorski in his directorial debut.
It stars Melanie Vincz, Raven De La Croix, and Angela Aames as women who infiltrate a
fortified island ruled by an undead wizard (Angus Scrimm) his evil cult.
The premiered on June 22, 1984 in Wilmington, North Carolina;
followed by a general release in February 1985.
The film explores themes of monster, undead, sword fight, death match.